[{"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #0", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u7d75", "answer": "\u3048 - painting; picture; drawing"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #1", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u6620\u753b\u9928", "answer": "\u3048\u3044\u304c\u304b\u3093 - movie theater"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #2", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u5916\u56fd\u4eba", "answer": "\u304c\u3044\u3053\u304f\u3058\u3093 - foreigner"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #3", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u5bb6\u5177", "answer": "\u304b\u3050 - furniture"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #4", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u89b3\u5149", "answer": "\u304b\u3093\u3053\u3046 - sightseeing"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #5", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u7d50\u5a5a\u5f0f", "answer": "\u3051\u3063\u3053\u3093\u3057\u304d - wedding"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #6", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u5730\u9707", "answer": "\u3058\u3057\u3093 - earthquake"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #7", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u7de0\u3081\u5207\u308a", "answer": "\u3057\u3081\u304d\u308a - deadline"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #8", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u30b8\u30e3\u30b1\u30c3\u30c8", "answer": "\u30b8\u30e3\u30b1\u30c3\u30c8 - jacket"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #9", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u7fd2\u6163", "answer": "\u3057\u3085\u3046\u304b\u3093 - custom"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #10", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u7a0e\u91d1", "answer": "\u305c\u3044\u304d\u3093 - tax"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #11", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u5352\u696d\u5f0f", "answer": "\u305d\u3064\u304e\u3087\u3046\u3057\u304d - graduation ceremony"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #12", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u305d\u3070", "answer": "\u305d\u3070 - Japanese buckwheat noodle"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #13", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u5730\u56f3", "answer": "\u3061\u305a - map"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #14", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u96fb\u6c60", "answer": "\u3067\u3093\u3061 - battery"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #15", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u5ead", "answer": "\u306b\u308f - garden"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #16", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u767a\u8868", "answer": "\u306f\u3063\u3074\u3087\u3046 - presentation"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #17", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u756a\u7d44", "answer": "\u3070\u3093\u3050\u307f - broadcast program"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #18", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u30d7\u30fc\u30eb", "answer": "\u30d7\u30fc\u30eb - swimming pool"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #19", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u30da\u30c3\u30c8", "answer": "\u30da\u30c3\u30c8 - pet"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #20", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u4e88\u5b9a", "answer": "\u3088\u3066\u3044 - schedule"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #21", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u65c5\u9928", "answer": "\u308a\u3087\u304b\u3093 - inn"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #22", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u5272\u5f15\u5238", "answer": "\u308f\u308a\u3073\u304d\u3051\u3093 - discount coupon"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #23", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u5e83\u3044", "answer": "\u3072\u308d\u3044 - spacious; wide"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #24", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u58f2\u308b", "answer": "\u3046\u308b - to sell"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #25", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u4e0b\u308d\u3059", "answer": "\u304a\u308d\u3059 - to withdraw (money)"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #26", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u304b\u304f", "answer": "\u304b\u304f - to draw; to paint"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #27", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u63a2\u3059", "answer": "\u3055\u304c\u3059 - to look for"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #28", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u8a98\u3046", "answer": "\u3055\u305d\u3046 - to invite"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #29", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u4ed8\u304d\u5408\u3046", "answer": "\u3064\u304d\u3042\u3046 - (1) to date (someone) (2) to keep company"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #30", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u7740\u304f", "answer": "\u3064\u304f - to arrive"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #31", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u4fdd\u967a\u306b\u5165\u308b", "answer": "\u307b\u3051\u3093\u306b\u306f\u3044\u308b - to buy insurance"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #32", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u6c17\u3092\u3064\u3051\u308b", "answer": "\u304d\u3092\u3064\u3051\u308b - to be cautious/careful"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #33", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u8abf\u3079\u308b", "answer": "\u3057\u3089\u3079\u308b - to look into (a matter)"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #34", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u6368\u3066\u308b", "answer": "\u3059\u3066\u308b - to throw away"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #35", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u898b\u3048\u308b", "answer": "\u307f\u3048\u308b - to be visible"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #36", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u3059\u308b", "answer": "\u3059\u308b - to decide on (an item)"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #37", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u5352\u696d\u3059\u308b", "answer": "\u305d\u3064\u304e\u3087\u3046\u3059\u308b - to graduate (from ...)"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #38", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u4e88\u7d04\u3059\u308b", "answer": "\u3088\u3084\u304f\u3059\u308b - to reserve"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #39", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u4e00\u65e5\u4e2d", "answer": "\u3044\u3061\u306b\u3061\u3058\u3085\u3046 - all day long"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch15 #40", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u6700\u8fd1", "answer": "\u3055\u3044\u304d\u3093 - recently"}], "wrongAnswer": []}]